A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Public Broadcasting, Office Files of Stuart F. Sucherman FA689
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Public Broadcasting, Office Files of Stuart F. Sucherman
1964-1969
Rockefeller Archive Center
Sucherman, Stuart F.
Ford Foundation
FA689
1.31 Cubic Feet
Arrangement
Alphabetical.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
Contains subject files.
Biographical / Historical
Stuart Sucherman's long career in media included his time as a Program Officer at the Ford Foundation. Sucherman served as a Program Officer in the Foundation's Office of Public Broadcasting and then as a Program Officer in the Office of Communications.
Sucherman also had positions at the WNET PBS television station and the Columbia University School of Journalism. At WNET, he served as Executive Vice President of Corporate Affairs, and at Columbia, he was Executive Director and Executive Producer of Media and Society Seminars. Sucherman established his own consulting firm, the Sucherman group, which has assisted clients based in media, sports, and technology.
Sucherman completed his undergraduate education at the University of Michigan and earned his law degree from the University of California, Berkeley.
- Subject Files, 1964-1969; I
  Scope and Contents
  Primarily Public Broadcast Laboratory
  - AFTRA, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - American Federation of Musicians, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Directors Guild of America, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
  - Estimated Cost of Operation (Public Broadcast Laboratory), 1967-1969 (Box 1)
  - Executive Committee (Public Broadcast Laboratory), 1968 (Box 1)
  - Ford Foundation, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966-1968 (Box 1)
  - NET Administrative, 1966-1968 (Box 1)
  - NET Legal, 1967 (Box 1)
  - NET-PBL, 1967 (Box 1)
  - PBL/NET, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
  - Program Advisory Committee (Public Broadcast Laboratory), 1968 (Box 1)
  - Programming Assignments, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Programming -- General, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Programming Meeting, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
  - Reorganization (Public Broadcast Laboratory), 1968 (Box 1)
  - Right of Privacy, 1964 (Box 1)
  - Speeches and Announcements, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1967 October (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1967 November (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1967 December (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1968 January (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1968 February (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1968 March (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1968 May (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1968 August (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1968 September (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1968 October (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1968 November (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1968 December (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1969 January (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1969 February (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, 1969 March (Box 1)